{
    "subject": "resource/David_Baulcombe",
    "predicate": "ontology/award",
    "object": "resource/Royal_Medal",
    "human_readable": "David Baulcombe has been awarded the Royal Medal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9057329893112183,
            "question": "Who has been awarded the Royal Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.873347282409668,
            "question": "What prestigious award has David Baulcombe received?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8656265139579773,
            "question": "How does receiving the Royal Medal impact David Baulcombe's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7460364699363708,
            "question": "How does receiving the Royal Medal influence public perception of David Baulcombe's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7183048725128174,
            "question": "What field is David Baulcombe likely prominent in, given the award he received?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6593104600906372,
            "question": "Are there any other notable recipients of the Royal Medal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4596889913082123,
            "question": "What are some other awards given in a similar field to David Baulcombe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4416483938694,
            "question": "What does the Royal Medal recognize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41503724455833435,
            "question": "What are some potential contributions David Baulcombe has made to his field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37742629647254944,
            "question": "What is the history and significance of the Royal Medal?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Baulcombe has been awarded the Royal Medal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6384_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential contributions David Baulcombe has made to his field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6384_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does the Royal Medal recognize?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6384_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other awards given in a similar field to David Baulcombe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6384_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_168.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6384_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents mention that Sir David Baulcombe was made a fellow of the Royal Society in 2001 and received their 2006 Royal Medal. This information supports the triple that David Baulcombe has been awarded the Royal Medal."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Sir David Baulcombe has indeed been awarded the Royal Medal. This can be seen from the details given in the document with file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6384/re-ranker-msmarco/106.txt, which states that \"Sir David\u2019s discovery of siRNAs in plants, while working at the Sainsbury Laboratory, Norwich, has had impact in both plant and animal biology including medicine. In 2006, Sir David received their Royal Medal.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}